Previously on:
Why don't you move in with me?
What?
Yeah, you and Ava
move in with me.
I love you,
and I want you in my life,
I want... I want
to have a future with you.
If Ava and I move in,
isn't somebody going
to have to move out?
Hmm.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
That's the ticket.
Yes. Out with the bad.
Morning.
Hey, I'm glad you're up.
I wanted...
Oh, whoa.
Sorry.
Is that really
a good workout?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's great for the circulation,
stretches the spine.
Your ball is hanging out.
Oopsie-daisy.
Back in the barn.
Wha... All right, listen, uh,
it's spring break this week,
so Zoey and her daughter
are going to stay here.
Oh, that's nice.
Yeah, it's kind of like
a... trial run.
You know, see what it's like
to live together
before we decide
to do anything permanent.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Living together is tricky.
Ball.
Sorry.
Of course it's going
to be a little tight
with all of us living here.
Yeah.
That's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
Oh, don't worry. I'll tell Jake
to go to his mom's.
Good, good.
And I'll make myself scarce.
You won't even know I'm here.
Oop.
Stepped on a duck.
All right, actually,
I'm going to need you to, uh,
move out for the week.
What, wait, the whole week?
Yeah, you and Zoey
don't really gel,
so, I just thought
it'd be for the best.
Oh, oh, that's fine.
Uh, but, uh, you know,
just for the record, I gel
with pretty much everybody.
I mean, ask around,
I'm positively gelatinous.
I know, it's her.
So, the plan is, I come
back after a week?
Uh, you might want to think of
this as a trial run of your own.
I mean, in case
Zoey and I do decide to
live together permanently.
Sure, sure, I get it.
Uh, and, uh,
let me just add that
no one is rooting for your
personal happiness
more than I am.
That's good to hear.
Thanks, man.
Oh, no, no, no.
Thank you, buddy.
No reason to panic.
Just got to find
a temporary new home...
...and three new balls.
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x21 ♪
Mr. Hose Says Yes
Original Air Date on April 16, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
What are you doing?
I'm taking a break.
Didn't you just get here?
Yeah.
Anyway,
I just wanted
to give you a heads up
that Zoey's going to stay here
for the week.
Uh-huh.
And she's bringing her daughter.
How old?
Seven.
See ya in a week.
Oh, come on, Berta.
You'll love her.
She's adorable.
Maybe to her mother,
and someone who's trying to get
into her mother's pants.
All right, look, it's not going
to be any extra work for you.
What ever Zoey doesn't
take care of, I'll handle.
Really?
You're going to take care
of a seven-year-old?
Yeah.
We get a long great.
And besides,
I got to learn sometime.
I mean, if Zoey and I get
married, I'll be Ava's stepdad.
You know, once upon a time,
a cute little boy came to live
in this house for a few days.
Maybe you've met him.
He's the pot-soaked
masturbating couch potato
who eats all your cookies.
Is he the one who
finished off my macaroons?
Your macaroons and my pot.
My point being,
fool me once, shame on you.
Fool me twice, I want a fully
funded 401 and a Camaro.
Come on, Berta, it's just
going to be for a week,
and it's just
the three of us.
Really? Did Zippy
finally hang himself?
No.
He's going to
stay somewhere else.
Zoey and I want to see what it's
like to live like a family,
with a housekeeper.
Who's got a retirement plan
and a muscle car.
All right, look, Berta, if you
don't want to help me with this,
I will find another housekeeper
who's willing to do very little
work for a very large salary
in a Malibu beach house.
You're cute,
but you got a mean streak.
All right, here we are.
What do you think?
Oh, boy, the ocean!
Stay on the deck!
Oh, she's so excited, she didn't
sleep at all last night.
Yeah, I'm kind of excited, too.
Really? I'm terrified.
Why?
Well, because if this little
experiment doesn't work,
it pretty much means
we're done, doesn't it?
Wow, now I'm terrified, too.
Oh, hey, there she is,
the new queen of the castle,
uh, milady.
Hello, Alan.
Thank you so much
for letting my boyfriend
use his own house
for the week.
Snidely put.
Thank you.
So, where are you staying?
Uh, well, I was thinking that
I was going to rent a suite
at the Bel Air Hotel,
uh, but then I realized
that cost money
and I have none.
So, um, I'm just going
to stay with Lyndsey.
How wonderful for her.
So, um,
all right, I will, uh,
I will see you in a week.
See ya.
In a week.
Yeah.
Say it.
I'll see ya in a week.
Okay, you two have fun.
All right.
Oh, oh, wait.
What room are you planning
to put the little girl in?
Yours.
Oh, oh, well, then I better
get a few things out of there.
Mostly magazines.
Maybe we should put her
in Jake's room.
No, that's actually worse.
♪ Men. ♪
You ready for another beer?
Oh, aren't you a doll.
You know...
Eldridge is with his
father this week.
Whoo, and Jake's with his mother.
Mmm.
So, I guess we can
do anything we want.
Yeah, and what do you want,
you dirty girl?
Well, you know what would
make me really happy?
Whatever it is,
I'll do it.
The guest toilet is broken.
I want you to fix it.
Uh, are we role-playing?
Am I the naughty plumber
here to snake your drain?
No.
You're the loving boyfriend
here to fix my toilet.
Seriously?
Seriously.
Now?
Now.
All right.
Hey, uh, when you're
done with that,
would you take the patio
furniture out of the garage
and put it in the backyard?
Sure.
Make sure you wash it first.
You got it.
Yep, I got it, all right.
I forgot a few things.
I'm going to run to the store.
Oh, you know, relax.
I'll go for you.
Actually, there's things
I need to buy
that I'd rather
you not know I need.
Say no more.
Put your coat on, Ava.
I don't want to go-- I'm playing.
Ava, come on.
No, she's fine.
I'll watch her.
You sure?
Yeah, of course.
It's no big deal.
Do you want to
stay here with Walden?
Yes, please.
Okay. See you in about an hour
Bye.
The sweet, sweet smell
of freedom.
Oh.
Hi.
I'm bored.
I thought you were playing
with your dolls.
I finished.
What do you want to do?
Well...
(Cyndi Lauper's "Girls Just Want
to Have Fun" plays)
♪ I come home
in the morning light ♪
♪ My mother says, "When you
gonna live your life right?" ♪
♪ Oh, mother dear,
we're not the fortunate ones ♪
♪ And girls,
they want to have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls
just want to have fun ♪
♪ ♪
♪ The phone rings
in the middle of the night ♪
♪ My father yells, "What you
gonna do with your life?" ♪
♪ Oh, daddy dear, you know
you're still number one ♪
♪ But girls,
they want to have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just want to have ♪
♪ That's all they really want ♪
♪ Some fun ♪
♪ When the working day is done ♪
♪ Oh, girls,
they want to have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just want
to have... ♪
There's my good girl.
Hi, Mommy.
Where's Walden?
Right there.
He said it's his nap time.
♪ Men. ♪
I think I found your problem!
You have got
a blown out fuse!
Can you fix it?
I don't see any
spare fuses but, uh,
I do know a little trick.
What's that?
Well, most people
don't know this,
but you can use
an ordinary copper penny
to replace a fuse.
No kidding?
Yeah, electricians
won't tell you
'cause they
want to charge you...
It worked! The TV's back on!
♪ Men. ♪
"They were married
soon after,
"and lived happily together
for many, many years.
The end."
Big surprise, huh?
Thank God.
It's too dark.
Oh, sorry. Here you go.
That's too bright.
Okay. Uh... how about...
I turn the bathroom light on
and leave the door open a crack?
How's that?
Better.
All right.
Good night.
Did you look under the bed?
No. Why, did you find
some funny magazines?
You have to check for monsters.
Oh.
Nope, no monsters.
Okay. Good night.
What about the closet?
What about it?
Monsters.
I don't want to have nightmares.
Right.
It's all clear.
Aah... great.
Now I'm gonna have nightmares.
Okay, okay, good night.
I'm thirsty.
You're joking.
Why would I joke about thirsty?
Thirsty's not funny.
I'll get you a glass of water.
No, I want fizzy water.
You want Perrier?
Pellegrino would be fine.
Okay.
I'll go see what we have.
How did the story end?
Uh... they got married,
and they lived happily together
for many, many years.
Till they had kids.
♪ Men. ♪
How are you feeling?
All right.
My hand's still a little numb.
Well, let's see if I can
make it all better.
Mmm...
Ooh! Ooh!
Make it all better.
Daddy like.
Mmm...
Did you hear something?
Mm, nothing but the
rustling in my jammies.
No!
There's someone downstairs.
No, there isn't. Come
on, make it all better.
Alan!
There's someone
in the house. Go look.
Really? With a dead hand and
the beginnings of an erection?
Go.
And thus ends the erection.
Who keeps their weed
in the crisper?
What, you want to get
crispy, don't you?
Ow!
Good morning.
It's still dark out.
It's breakfast time.
Maybe in London.
What's going on?
She wants breakfast.
Okay.
Just give me a minute.
No, you sleep;
I'll get it.
Thanks.
That's it? No argument?
Shh...
All right.
What do you want?
Corn Flakes or Cheerios or...
Eggs Benedict.
Of course.
♪ Men. ♪
Watch your step.
Yeah, wouldn't want
to get hurt.
Those pain pills starting
to kick in yet?
Oh, yeah.
You could spread me on a toast.
Okay.
Let's get you into bed.
No, no.
Let's get you into bed.
Seriously?
You want to fool around?
Parts of me do.
- Mr. Nose says, "No," but Mr.
- "Yes""
Tell you what,
why don't you just lie down
and let me take care of you.
Really?
You took care of me when I thought
there was someone in the house.
Oh, right, right, I did.
I was brave.
Let's just get this belt
and zipper undone.
Good thing you could breathe
through your nose.
- Ow! - What?!
Ball snag!
Oh, sorry!
No, no, don't touch it!
Don't...! Oh!
I think I broke Mr. Hose.
Hey!
What?
What in the hell
happened here?
I tried to make breakfast
for the kid.
"Tried"?
Yeah. The eggs were too runny,
so I made oatmeal
that was too dry,
so I made waffles
that were-- and I quote--
"Bloody dreadful."
Where is she now?
I don't know; I don't care.
I can't do this, Berta.
It's just... it's too much.
She just never stops.
Yeah, I raised
four daughters.
The only thing that slows them
down is jail and johnsons.
I told Zoey
we were gonna be a family.
What am I gonna do?
The kid's seven?
Yeah.
Wait nine years.
What happens in nine years?
If you're lucky, she runs away
with a coke-addled bass player.
And if I'm not lucky?
A drummer.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey.
Oh, you're up.
How are you feeling?
A little better.
I'm glad.
Not looking forward
to ripping the Band-Aid
off my scrotum, but...
we'll cross that bridge
when we get to it.
I'm so, so sorry.
Yeah, just...
FYI, if you'd like to try again,
I'm wearing sweatpants.
No zipper.
I cannot believe
you're still horny.
Me neither,
but there it is.
Well, I do owe you one.
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
Do you smell that?
Oh, don't worry.
That's just the Neosporin.
No.
It-it smells
like something dead.
It's not Mr. Hose.
He's very much alive.
Go ahead. Check.
I think it's coming
from under the house.
I'm sorry, I-I really
can't smell anything
'cause of my broken nose...
'cause of what you owe me.
It-it's probably just a raccoon
or a possum.
Hang on one sec.
Let me call the exterminator.
Oh, no, no, no,
that's going to take too long.
I'll ju... I'll just get
a shovel and a garbage bag
and deal with it.
You're that horny?
I know, it's starting
to worry me, too.
You okay down there?
Yeah. Yeah, I think I see it.
Looks like a-a dead possum.
Be careful.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I-I'm just going
to shovel him into my...
Not dead! Not dead!
Ow! Ow!
Yah! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean...
Ow! No! Ow!
Come on!
Oh, that's going
to get infected.
Ah! Ahh!
♪ Men. ♪
Thank you.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
Thanks for meeting me, man.
Whoa!
What happened to you?
Well, let's see, uh...
Electrocuted, got
my nose bashed in,
and possibly rabies.
How are you?
I am really tired.
My heart bleeds for you.
Also my left ball sack.
What's that smell?
Oh, Neosporin, which
just a hint of possum.
So, uh, how are things going
living with Zoey and her daughter?
It's good, it's good.
Oh.
How's living with Lyndsey?
Oh, it's terrific.
That's great.
If I could get rid of them...
Yes! A hundred times yes!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net